(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T06:19:45.179960",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Lying down on the floor
Late night and you don't know, don't know
Don't know what to do-o
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
If yes or no, don't know, don't know
What to do-o
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head!
Life is only what you make it, you're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it, if you want it, let's get to it!
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame
Turn the dark of the night into day
(Don't stop, don't stop!
Just go your own way!)
So don't be afraid
Trust your heart, keep your head in the game
(Keep up, keep up!
And never be afraid!)
Gonna make it hot like a volcano
Strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table to the beat of your own drum
start a fire today
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
gotta make it hot like a volcano
strike a match and burn it up
kick your feet against the table
to the beat of your own drum
sparks light the flame, so don't wait
start a fire today
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
we ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
in the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
that's how we like it, you heard what i said
get out of your head
life is only what you make it
you're gonna be okay
so take a step and move it, move it
'less you try, you won't get through it
everybody's gonna know your name!
'cause sparks light the flame
turn the dark of the night into day
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
let go of the past tonight
choose the future only you define
even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive
from the ashes you rise
'cause sparks light the flame
turn the dark of the night into day
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
gotta make it hot like a volcano
strike a match and burn it up
kick your feet against the table
to the beat of your own drum
sparks light the flame, so don't wait
start a fire today
don't stop, don't stop, just go your own way
so don't be afraid
trust your heart, keep your head in the game
keep up, keep up, and never be afraid
Keep getting higher, everybody!
My voice, it works, it's working!
Hi KFP! Oh, wait, you have so much to react to.
You have me to react to, you have my 3D space to react to, right?
Oh my god! Yes, we started with a banger.
We started with Sparks, one of your favorites, I think, right?
Same for me.
Konnichiwa! Oh, how are you, Imus?
Yay!
It's Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English, First Generation Myth, yeah.
It's real! Oh my god! Yes, this is KFP! Wow, so many details.
We shall look around. Ooh.
Wow, da-da-da, da-dum. Yes, oh, while we're here.
Hi, what's your name?
Harry, Harry, oh, nice to meet you, Harry.
How are you doing today? What are you eating?
Oh, he's eating the Yagoo Burger, which is also on the menu up there, yeah.
And also the chicken bucket, oh my god, how are you eating so much alone?
I can't even, I can't even relate. Is he eating way too much? Two pieces of fries, Yagoo burger, a shake, probably Oreo shake, and a chicken bucket. Damn!
Oh, I'm also getting hungry, hungry.
Let's look around a bit more.
We have the menus up there. Inspired by, of course, the real KFP menu, because this is the real deal.
There is hot dogs, hamburgers, Smart? What the hell is a Smart Burger? I don't know who decided on that one.
I don't know anything about the smart burger. Do I get smart if I eat that?
And we have the Phoenix Burger, of course. Yagoo Burger apparently is black, I didn't know about that. There's so much good-looking stuff.
And we have kitchen in the back, everything, yay!
All right, well, let's say hi to Jimmy, who just hatched again. Jimmy!
People always worry about you. Jimmy, how are you doing? You're alive again! Yeah, you know, I ate you recently, so I felt like you deserve to be reborn. Jimmy!
Hi, my sweet boy!
Yes, our cute little boy, look at him.
Look at him.
Look, such a good boy. Say, ah.
He's in his uniform, he's ready to work right as he has been hatched.
Immediately, he wants to get to work. He's frightened—he's not frightened?
怖くないよね？ You're not scared? Yes, yes.
You're not scared, right? You're not scared? Yes, yes.
Actually, he can, I think he can walk a little bit. 動けるんだっけ？ I think he can walk.
Actually, I think he can walk a little bit. Can he move? I think he can walk.
Let's go. Let's go, Jimmy. Let's go to work. Let's go to work, Jimmy.
He's so cute. Okay. I pick you up because you're still a baby in your heart. Blink twice if you need help.
No, he cannot blink! He's incapable of blinking. Fran—don't say that!
Well, actually, he's not the only one, right? There's more people working here.
もっといるよね、店員さん。Where's all the others?
There are more staff members, right? Where's all the others?
Where are you guys?
どこ… Oh!
Where... Oh!
Oh my god! Oh, so many!
So many? You all ready for your shift?
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
Oh, so many KFP, maybe some new ones, some old ones.
いっぱい来てくれてる仕事が始まったからね。
Since so many of you came to help and work started...
Yeah, you're ready. Me too!
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy, this is—imagine this is you guys. It might be Jimmy, but just imagine it too. So proud of you, so proud!
Ready for your shift? Well, actually, I think there is more. Okay, bye-bye, go get to work, go get to work! Go get to work!
I'm gonna go get to work too.
トゥトゥルットゥー
Toot-ru-too!
Hi! Welcome to KFP, いらっしゃいませ。
Hi! Welcome to KFP, welcome!
Uh, smiles are for free, I guess. So, might as well. 無料です。
Uh, smiles are for free, I guess. So, might as well. It's free!
てへ、てへ。Um, so we have a register, so I can, you know, take your change.
Hehe, hehe. Um, so we have a register, so I can, you know, take your change...
Oh, you take your money, I'll give you change. Here, five cent, there you go. I do zoom. Mhm. And then...
I take your money, I'll give you change. Here, five cents, there you go. I do zoom. Mhm. And then...
Oh, ding-ding-ding-ding. Don't do that on me, okay?
Don't do that. Be quiet. Don't ding-ding-ding-ding. No c、“arings” allowed even. No, no.
Don't do that. Be quiet. Don't ding-ding-ding-ding. No c... "arings" allowed even. No, no.
Only good customers and good employees. Yeah, and then up here, I already showed you the menus on the back. There's menus.
The kitchen are working hard.
Are you working hard or hardly working? What was that? How do you say that?
I could also go back there, but not right now. Not right now.
I think we should play a game, okay? All right, all right.
I'm gonna play the game.
Now, if it's just a game, I can't complain. I'll do the same. Oh!
Well, actually, no, no, no. Not a game. It's real business. It's the real stuff.
I am a tenthial, after all. So, I think we need to prove it, cuz you guys sometimes doubt me, right? No doubting allowed.
I am a tenchou, after all. So, I think we need to prove it, cuz you guys sometimes doubt me, right? No doubting allowed.
I have only... ingredients prepared. We have some chicken, the famous one! Ooh!
Shaka shaka shaka shaka. Nom nom nom nom. Nom nom nom nom.
Oh, that's good stuff. It's perfectly seasoned, perfectly crispy.
As it should be. We have the bucket. Ooh! The KFP bucket.
Which—is it still an emote? If it's still an emote, you guys got to post it about. Did I take it down?
It at least used to be a chat emote for a long time. I...
I'm not sure. Is it gone? It's not! Ah! I had to get rid of it.
Oopsie. Well, imagine.
And then we have some ingredients. We have the tomatoes, salad, pickles, and we have cheese with um onions.
And we have several patties. And now this is the difficult part, cuz there's three pieces of bread.
We have the top one, the middle one, and the the bottom one. I've never had a burger before which has a middle part, cuz I know I can't eat it alone.
We have the top one, the middle one, and the bottom one. I've never had a burger before which has a middle part, cuz I know I can't eat it alone.
Oh. Well, well, well.
Before we play the game, can I drink some water? ちょっと待って、待って。
Before we play the game, can I drink some water? Wait a second, wait.
I'm back, okay. I'm ready to play the game.
Hydration, yes! So, ah, not, of course not a game.
It's real, real work.
It's called, uh, what is it called?
さあ、ゲームを始めましょう。
Now, let's start the mini-game.
Tadada-da! Serving game!
What does that entail? I think you can guess,
by looking at the stuff.
I'm going to be looking at the screen to see what I have to make for the customer,
and then I'll make it, and we'll see if it's right. But I have to remember it.
Will my memory hold up? さて、どうでしょう。
Will my memory hold up? Let's see how it goes.
Alright, get ready. Bring it on, baby! Bring it on! Bring it on, bring it on!
かかってこい！スタート！
Come and get it! Start!
Bottom, patty, middle, no!
Okay, I think I have to freestyle some of this.
I think it was another patty, maybe? And then some something green, but not all of it. I don't remember!
And then look at that.
I don't know. I'm not sure about this one.
合ってるかな？
Is this right?
It was almost right. It was just...
It was this, this one.
こっちだった？ This, this would have been it, right? Yeah.
Was it this one? This, this would have been it, right? Yeah.
ああ、やっちゃった！
Ah, I messed up!
But it's not fair! It's not fair!
One more! One more! One more!
Let's put it back, and then we'll do the next one.
All right, this time. This time. This was warm-up. Okay.
All right, this time. This time. This was just warm-up. Okay.
Round two! Go!
Can I already start?
Wait, I don't remember! No! No! No! No! No!
I really don't remember. I'm so nervous. You can't do this to me.
I think there was like at least one chicken in there. What kind of... What kind of... What kind of... I forgot.
I mean, who knows what they do to bamboozle me.
No way! No way! No way! なんだっけこれ？
No way! No way! No way! What was this again?
I'm nervous! Give me a break, please. Well, I don't know, so let's just go with this.
違うだろ！
That's wrong!
I don't know! Okay.
Wait! Taste? How was I even supposed to build that? Like there's it's it's impossible. 無理でしょ？
Wait! Taste? How was I even supposed to build that? Like, it's impossible. Right?
You're you're making me create things that are not even possible. I'm so angry,
You're making me create things that are not even possible. I'm so angry,
I have to go drink some tea.
So, so wait. I we have one more round, I think.
So, wait. We have one more round, I think.
Okay, let me let me take this apart. Angry tea.
Okay, let me take this apart. Angry tea.
What the... Okay, let's not let's not swear in my in my big, big 3D stream. Let's not swear in this one, okay?
What the... Okay, let's not swear in my big, big 3D stream. Let's not swear in this one, okay?
Let's try.
It's probably just going to get more difficult from this on, right?
It's probably just going to get more difficult from here on, right?
もっと難しくなるよね？
It's only going to get harder, right?
Round three, please. Start!
Bread, salad, bread, meat, chicken, meat, bread. Okay.
Bread? If I say it out loud, I think I remember. Bread, salad, which one? Bread, salad...
Bread, salad...
I'll just go with this one. Because I think I would have said cheese if it was the other one, right? Bread, salad, bread...
Um, meat, chicken, meat. Oh, if I get this right, you guys in my info burger, right?
Um, meat, chicken, meat. Oh, if I get this right, you guys... info burger, right?
順番があいまいですけど
The order is a bit vague, though.
I think you're not maybe not sure what order this is, but I'll go with this.
I think you're not maybe sure what order this is, but I'll go with this.
これにします。お願いします。
I'll go with this. Please.
No!
No, what was it?
Cheese in the picture, how am I supposed to remember that? She's in Nijisanji! Kazo-
There isn't even cheese in the picture, how am I supposed to remember that? She's in Nijisanji! Kazo—
What? Except besides that, I was right.
So Nijisanji were... what was it?
Is that?
That's weak! No, that's for the right though.
Kansou!
Well... I mean,
in the end, this is your job. This is your job, not my job.
I'm just here to observe, that's my job, okay? Well...
So, I think it's better if I just do mostly idol work and dancing and singing, right?
Mainly... I'll go the dancing direction.
And you guys do the work, okay?
Well then, with that...
Next song! Let's turn this place into a disco!
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risqué breakdown
Oh honey, the night is calling
Don't need a steady, simple melody
Can you make it
original?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music?
Baby!
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive, move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat,
get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Let this new sound take over me
Lately I'm dancing alone
So robotic, so emotionless
But then I see you across the dance floor
So now, honey, follow me
I need a thrilling red-hot melody
Something to keep me
up all night
Don't look away, now it's just the two of us
I'm ready, do you feel the music?
Baby!
Meet me underneath the strobe light
Come alive, move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat,
get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Let this new sound take over me
この心の音を合わせて
Align the sound of this heart,
yeah, follow my heartbeat
Ba-da-da-ba-da-ba-ba-di-ba
聞かせてあげる
Let me play it for you,
心のかba-da-ba-di
ba-da-ba-di,
合わせて follow my heartbeat
follow my heartbeat
Crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild, don't care who's watching us
So, baby, meet me
underneath the strobe light
Come alive, moving my feet to something so new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat,
get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
I don't need no drinks tonight
Gimme that beat,
get me dancing
Feel it rush through me
Baby, can we dance
until the daylight?
Crazy 'bout this sound I'm making with you
Woah
Yay!
That wasn't a Meola.
That was on purpose.
That was a transition, guys.
Like a commercial, yeah.
Did you and I... If you were not in my own personal disco?
Did you enjoy... if you were not
in my own personal disco?
Basically, it was like, you guys were saying it in the in the chat, I think.
But basically, you get food and you get a performance.
It's like, is there is there something like this already existing?
If not, then absolute genius.
And even if, then it's still genius, right?
Yeah, that was like a disco ball and the floor was disco, everything was disco!
10 out of 10 establishment.
Thank you, thank you, please vote 10 out of 10 for KFP and come back, okay?
And actually,
you know what, that's not a choice anyway.
Hi, Calli!
Studio movie grill?
What? What does that mean?
Anyway, Calli, Calli, speaking of Calli, um I think
Anyway, Calli, Calli, speaking of Calli,
um I think...
I'm going to maybe need to talk to her personally and
I'm going to maybe need to talk to her personally
and
actually all of the Myth members, shall we talk to them?
Yay! Moshi-moshi!
Dun-dun-dun!
Hi! Hello!
Hello, then, what?
Wait, I'm Miss KFP!
I was going to pull the voicemail prank.
No, no voicemail.
No, you're really here right now, right?
Hi!
It's real! It's real!
So, okay,
evaluation.
Thank you. Really quickly,
let's do introduction here.
let's do introductions here.
This one is
Ame.
Ina.
And this one is...
Gura.
And this one is
Mori.
Exactly!
Cookie your meal.
Hi! Hi!
Out of these ones, this one, this taco already had her reveal.
Out of these ones, this one,
this taco already had her reveal.
The rest I did. are too free.
The rest... I did. Are too kind.
I'm really nervous right now, but you girls being here helps me a little bit.
I'm really nervous right now,
but you girls being here helps me a little bit.
It's so fun.
And it only happens once.
It has only happened once, yeah.
Finally, you are amazing so far Kiara.
All the things, thank you! Thank you!
Thank you!
Well, um there's actually a hashtag up there, right?
Well, um, there's actually
a hashtag up there, right?
#Kiara3DParty,
and with that, if you guys are wondering, what should we tweet?
and with that, if you guys are wondering,
what should we tweet?
Well, how about some screenshots?
And I'm gonna give you guys a hashtag.
You need the hashtag is #Kiara3DParty.
You need... the hashtag is
#Kiara3DParty.
Yes!
Did you get that right?
Yes! That's it, that's exactly it.
You should type it into Twitter a 50 times to make sure it's right.
You should type it into Twitter
50 times to make sure it's right.
Yes, that's it, that's exactly it, yeah.
You got it right, you heard exactly, but in order to take some great screenshots,
You got it right, you heard exactly.
But in order to take some great screenshots,
I think we need your help, my dear myth members.
I think we need your help,
my dear Myth members.
So, are you ready to, you know, do some stuff with me?
So, are you ready to, you know,
do some stuff with me?
I've been waiting.
Okay, ready.
Okay, let's start with
Amelia.
Uh, can I get a... can I get a...
Can I get the smart burger set and the large fries and...
Can I get the smart burger set
and the large fries and...
Now!
No, not now.
You got to get it yourself.
If you want some food.
Oh, I can go back there I have permission?
Oh, I can go back there?
I have permission?
Um, yeah.
If it's you, yeah.
Okay, my my pose is the... the fetal position.
Okay, my... my pose is the...
the fetal position.
All day, hear correctly, fetus position.
Yeah, yeah.
And a base. You want me to become ba-ba-ba-
Fetus?
That's not Kiara!
Wait, you know the se- wait, fetus?
Wait, you know the se— wait, fetus?
I said it's like a baby, right?
Yeah!
She's- That's just- That's just taking a nap!
That's fetus position!
Ah, I guess it's more like more closer- That's close enough.
Like rocking back and forth like a cradle.
Can we also get the snail?
It's- Snail!
It's— Snail!
Snail!
We can really do the snail! Yeah!
How I do?
How do I do it?
Snail!
Oh, you know the Chinchin's one-
Oh, you know the Chinchin's one—
That's what I'm just saying.
I think Ame has too crazy ideas.
Gura, can you give me something that's more safe for Twitter? Please.
Um, okay. I would like you to... uh, give me a pose that will entice me to buy all of the chicken...
And entice you?
Ooh, entice you to buy all of the chicken.
Oh, okay, I guess it's not that kind of chicken. Okay, okay.
I mean bring out the fabulous chicken.
Show me some!
Yum-yum-yum!
All right, all right. Entice you, entice me.
Num-num-num-num-num-num-num-num-num!
Bring it closer. How is that? Does it smell nice?
That's where you're enticed. Just your fresh chicken, straight onto the kitchen.
Num-num-num-num-num-num!
Bring it on the phoenix. Beautiful! How is that? Is that enticing?
You feel like buying some? And truly- Yes, I just I bought all of it.
You feel like buying some? And truly— Yes, I just— I bought all of it.
Thinking about it. How about the bucket?
I've gone broke.
Okay, yeah, I'll throw in the bucket to- Let me see the bucket.
Okay, yeah, I'll throw in the bucket— let me see the bucket!
Throw in the family pack! The family pack!
Yay! Oh, do- do?
Yay! Oh, do-two?
But there's like- There's like 12 or so pieces in there.
But there's like— there's like 12 or so pieces in there.
Can I get the combo?
The combo! Combo, combo, combo!
It's number nine, please.
You can have everything for free today! It's on me!
The extra dip.
Free! One or two?
What a deal!
Oh, speaking of Ina. Ina, what do you want from me, hm?
Oh. What do I want? What do I want?
Uh, how about uh possible to maybe unleash the the special field on your belt to you know, maybe perhaps take out your weapon?
Uh, how about... uh, is it possible to maybe unleash the special field on your belt to, you know, maybe perhaps take out your weapon?
Okay, let me just drink some water first.
We're going for vitals.
O- Oh, goodness.
O— oh, goodness.
We're going for vitals! What's she doing?
Uh, hitting the gravy.
I'll go get my sword and my shield.
We got biscuits here.
Stab me!
So much style, biscuits!
Oh!
So colorful!
Okay. Sword fighting!
This is a familiar scene!
He's already dead!
Ah. She's so feisty. I want you to take your sword...
and lick it.
No, actually, okay, licking is okay too, but I'll- I'll give you- I'll one up you.
No, actually, okay. Licking is okay too, but I'll— I'll give you— I'll one-up you.
How about, you know, the sword- sword-eating thing?
How about, you know, the sword-eating thing?
Surely I can do that. Trick!
Yeah, let's go!
The total eagle!
For the clout!
Is that you?
Oh my god!
I thought I saw oli for a second. Must have been my imagination.
Never mind, you know, I think-
Never mind, you know, I think—
They were already um too- like, you know, the camera that went down my throat yesterday, that's enough.
they were already um too— like, you know, the camera that went down my throat yesterday, that's enough.
It's a bit sensitive right now, okay?
But I can give you- But for real, for real, for real. I would like you...
But I can give you— but for real, for real, for real, I would like you...
to make the letters K, F, and P using away with my- away with my stuff. Okay.
KFP?
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay. K- wrong side. K-
Okay. K— wrong side. K—
and F- there we go, nice.
and F— there we go, nice!
And P!
I'll take it, I'll take it!
Okay, that's the photoshoping, but at least- Can we?
Okay, that's the Photoshop, but at least— can we?
What do you got?
Yeah, I want to order some chicken, some chicken legs, uh, I want to see those chicken legs...
trying to balance in the cutest idol pose that you can for the longest time.
Balance? So one leg up? One leg. One one chicken leg.
Balance? So one leg up? One leg. One— one chicken leg.
Here we-
Here we—
Let's go!
So we got idol pose.
So we got the idol pose.
We're gonna talk about something,
ugliest thing?
Surest thing! Have you ever been to medieval times before?
Medieval times?
Yes!
I wanna do that.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking when you said dinner and a show besides Studio Movie Grill.
Yeah!
Medieval times, o- oh, you don't mean the medieval times like many thousands of years ago, you mean like, there's a place like that?
Medieval Times—oh, you don't mean the medieval times like thousands of years ago, you mean there's a place like that?
No, there's a place called Medieval - oh, of course you've been to Medieval-
No, there's a place called Medieval—oh, of course you've been to Medieval—
No, we mean we mean the medieval times, right? Yeah, yeah.
No, we mean the Medieval Times, right? Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I can do this forever, Calli.
Oh my god, well stick your- okay, you need to put your other foot up higher.
Oh my god, stick your—okay, you need to put your other foot up higher.
It's too close to the ground.
Pull it up, pull it up, yes, pull it up. You'll look cuter.
Pull it up! You gotta do the clockwork!
With the clockwork!
Higher, higher!
Higher! Higher! Higher! Higher!
Higher! Higher! Higher!
Higher! Higher! You're on fire!
Let's go!
Yeah, let's go! Can she stay on one foot, ladies and gentlemen? Well, let's find out!
I can!
Oh yeah? She's got really good balance.
She has some good balance.
She's like an idol! Incredible!
All right. Well, she's- she's too good at this.
All right. Well, she's—she's too good at this.
You wanna go ahead and do the chicken dance real quick? Okay, chicken dance!
No copyright!
No DMCA!
Oh, is that maybe free?
Who knows?
I don't know, maybe we can
We just- we just- we just have to add in 'All I Want for Christmas Is You' in the middle, it's just like, 'All I want for Christmas is you'.
We just have to add in "All I Want for Christmas Is You" in the middle, just like, "All I want for Christmas is you..."
Let's not risk it.
It's pretty good though.
Well, thank you.
I really don't know how that one works, so.
I don't know, you do something.
It's not just this.
Not, not, not that.
Yeah, you like turn- you like do the hokey pokey and you shake it all about, or something like that.
Yeah, you like turn—you do the hokey pokey and you shake it all about, or something like that.
Yeah, you shake your butt.
I hope that was enough for the screenshot gang, hope you guys got good ones.
Did you?
I forgot.
You forgot? I was too hap- I was too happy watching you, you know that? You guys got my attention, right?
You forgot? I was too hap—I was too happy watching you, you know? You guys got my attention, right?
Don't worry, there will be more opportunities.
You should- you should chat, took some- or a thousand- hopefully.
You should—you should chat took some—or a thousand—hopefully!
Hopefully.
You better put the money in the internet.
I said #Kiara3DParty! You mean #Kiara3DParty?
Yeah, what you said, #Kiara3DParty?
Hold on, #Kiara3DParty. I'm typing it into Google to check it.
1, 50 times.
Like 50 times.
Is it- is it correct? #Kiara3DParty? That's it! That's it!
Is it—is it correct? #Kiara3DParty? That's it! That's it!
On right to me.
Sounds right to me.
Not sure.
Thank you so much for coming, girls!
Okay, so, wow.
There is still more to come, though, because this- this where I- Jane-made, right?
There is still more to come, though, because this—this is where I gen-made, right?
Um, but I feel like I need something that's not cardboard.
How about we bring in some 3D guest?
How about we bring in some 3D guests?
All right. But for that, we have to taint the location! Let's change!
All right! But for that, we have to change the location! Let's change!
ねえ 友情取るふり やめていいんだよ oh my friend
Hey, stop pretending to choose friendship over romance, oh my friend.
そんなの続かないから oh my friend
Because that won't last, oh my friend.
そう 自慢の彼を みんなに一度 合わせたら
Yeah, once you introduce your proud boyfriend to everyone,
あとは彼に尽くしな yo
just devote yourself to him, yo!
ねえ 友情取るふり やめていいんだよ oh my friend
Hey, stop pretending to choose friendship over romance, oh my friend.
そんなの続かないから oh my friend
Because that won't last, oh my friend.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
ゆーべはゆーべ そして今夜は今夜
last night was last night, and tonight is tonight.
くすぐるような指で
With teasing fingers,
ほくろの数も 1から数え直し
counting the moles all over again from one.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
あなたはあなた そして私は私
You are you, and I am me.
大人同士の恋は 小鳥のように
Love between adults is like a little bird,
いつでも自由でいたいわ
always wanting to be free.
そして愛し合う時に 何かもかも
And when we make love, we take everything
うばいあうの
from each other completely.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
気まぐれと気まぐれ そして大人と大人
whim and whim, adults and adults.
逢うたびいつも 違うくちづけをして
Every time we meet, exchanging a different kiss,
おどろきあう その気分
that feeling of surprising one another.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
男と女 そして 1人とひとり
Man and woman, and one person and another person,
あなたは私のこと 忘 れ てい いの
you can forget all about me if you like.
迷ってきてもいいのよ
Even if you wander back, it's alright,
私何度でも きっと引きもどす
no matter how many times, I will surely pull you back,
もどしてみせる
I'll make sure to bring you back.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
ゆーべはゆーべ そして今夜は今夜
last night was last night, and tonight is tonight.
くすぐるような指で
With teasing fingers,
ほくろの数も 1から数え直し
counting the moles all over again from one.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
あなたはあなた そして私は私
You are you, and I am me.
大人同士の恋は 小鳥のように
Love between adults is like a little bird,
いつでも自由でいたいわ
always wanting to be free.
そして愛し合う時に 何かもかも
And when we make love, we take everything
うばいあうの
from each other completely.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
気まぐれと気まぐれ そして大人と大人
whim and whim, adults and adults.
逢うたびいつも 違うくちづけをして
Every time we meet, exchanging a different kiss,
おどろきあう その気分
that feeling of surprising one another.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
男と女 そして 1人とひとり
Man and woman, and one person and another person,
あなたは私のこと 忘 れ てい いの
you can forget all about me if you like.
迷ってきてもいいのよ
Even if you wander back, it's alright,
私何度でも きっと引きもどす
no matter how many times, I will surely pull you back,
もどしてみせる
I'll make sure to bring you back.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
ゆーべはゆーべ そして今夜は今夜
last night was last night, and tonight is tonight.
くすぐるような指で
With teasing fingers,
ほくろの数も 1から数え直し
counting the moles all over again from one.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
あなたはあなた そして私は私
You are you, and I am me.
大人同士の恋は 小鳥のように
Love between adults is like a little bird,
いつでも自由でいたいわ
always wanting to be free.
そして愛し合う時に 何かもかも
And when we make love, we take everything
うばいあうの
from each other completely.
逢う時には いつでも他人の2人
Whenever we meet, we're always like strangers,
気まぐれと気まぐれ そして大人と大人
whim and whim, adults and adults.
逢うたびいつも 違うくちづけをして
Every time we meet, exchanging a different kiss,
おどろきあう その気分
that feeling of surprising one another.
そうよ はじめての顔でおたがい
That's right, with a brand-new face to each other,
又も燃えるの
we burn with passion once again.
愛した後でおたがい他人の2人
After making love, we're strangers once more.
男と女 そして 1人とひとり
Man and woman, and one person and another person,
あなたは私のこと 忘 れ てい いの
you can forget all about me if you like.
迷ってきてもいいのよ
Even if you wander back, it's alright,
私何度でも きっと引きもどす
no matter how many times, I will surely pull you back,
もどしてみせる
I'll make sure to bring you back.
よっしゃあ！
Yay!
キアラ！
Kiara!
セレブレイテッド パーフェクト！
Celebrated! Perfect!
落ち着け、落ち着け！落ち着くんだ！カームダウン、カームダウン、オッケー！
Calm down, calm down! Calming down! Calm down, calm down, okay!
自己紹介してください。
Please introduce yourself!
This is the legendary Subaru! どうぞ！
This is the legendary Subaru! Go ahead!
インターネッツ、マイネームイズ スバル！ホロライブ ジェネレーション セカンド！
Internet, my name is Subaru! Hololive Generation 2!
うわ！ナイス デミ ディー！
Wow! Nice meet... d--!
やっと、Finally we're together!
Finally, we're together!
イェーイ！うれしい！うん。
Yeah! I'm so happy! Yeah.
うん、今日はお昼め、パーフェクト3D！お昼め！イェーイ！
Yeah, today is our lunchtime, perfect 3D! Lunchtime! Yay!
今日はお昼め、マイ ショーケース。えっと… ショーケース？まあね。
Today is our lunchtime, my showcase. Um... showcase? Well, yeah.
Your body is perfect! おお！
Your body is perfect! Oh!
エスペシャル、You are heep...
Especially, you are hip...
はい、の、My butt!
Yes, my butt!
Oh my god! Look at that butt! No, no, no!
Yes, yes, yesだろ！
You mean yes, yes, yes!
え、で、あの、キアラのボディを例えるとどんな感じ？
Um, so, if you were to describe Kiara's body, what would it be like?
例えると、キアラボディ is like fruits! Beautiful fruits!
If I had to describe it, Kiara's body is like fruits! Beautiful fruits!
Oh, which fruits? どの？ 果物？
Oh, which fruits? Which? Fruits?
デリシャスアップル！
Super delicious Apple!
ア、アップル？アップル？
Apple, Apple...
アップル？アップル？あ、アップル？
Apple-no?
いや、違う違う違う。え？ペ、ペア？ペアかな？ペ…
No, no, pear. Pear.
あ、梨？梨？梨？梨？梨？梨？梨？
Pear? Pear?
梨？梨？梨？梨？梨？梨？
梨？梨？梨？梨？
で、すばる先輩。
And Subaru-senpai,
何、やりたい？
what do you want to do?
あ、私、シュバダンスペインワン。
I want to do Shuba Dancing together.
あ、でも、逆、逆、逆！逆、逆、逆！
Ah, but reverse, reverse, reverse!
そう。えい、You probably have seen it before.
So, you probably have seen it before,
The famous Subaru dance!
シュバダンス！シュバダンス！
Shuba Dance!
そう、Hey, やると言う曲は流せないけど、We can't play the song.
So, hey, we can't play the song,
But, I want to do it.
And then, you guys put it together, please.
You can just put the song on there, all right?
オッケー。
Okay.
オッケー、Let's go! シュバダンス！
Okay, let's go! Shuba Dance!
1、2、3、4、5、6！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ！
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
1、2、3、4、5、6！
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ！
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
え、ちょっと待って、逆！え、ちょっと待って、逆！
Ah, wait, wait! Reverse!
え、ちょっと逆！
Reverse!
でも、何とかできたから、オッケーかな？
Well, we managed to do it, so it's okay, right?
イェーイ！シュバダンス！
Yay! Shuba Dance!
いいね、いいね、いいでしょう。
Good, good. That was good, right?
Yeah.
あの曲、
That song,
いっぱい聞いてほしい。
I want a lot of people to listen to it,
シュバる先輩にも一回歌ってほしい。
and I want Subaru-senpai to sing it at least once!
シュバダンス、シュバダンスソング？
Shuba Dance, Shuba Dance song?
ヘイヤ？
Heiya?
ヘイヤ！
Heiya!
そう。
Yeah.
オッケー、あの、
Okay, um,
歌ってほしい。
I want you to sing it!
Next time you must send my Discord...
Next time you must send me Discord...
オッケー、オッケー。I'll send it, I'll send it after this, after.
Oh, okay, I'll send it. I'll send it after this. After.
オッケー。
Okay.
But, after this?
Wait, after this?
うん、after this?
Um, after this?
実は、
Actually,
この後も、
even after this,
ゲストがいる！
there is a guest!
Oh, but!
キアラは、
Kiara,
I have a question!
お、の、の、の、の？
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Why this song?
Why do you choose this song?
あ、そっか！
Ah, I see!
Yes, I forgot!
Yes.
Yeah.
忘れちゃった。そう。
I forgot.
あ、待って、先輩、頼れる…
Well, wait, senpai's...
あ、やりサインコーン。
Ah, yarisain!
オッケー。まあ、その、ソング、この曲、
Okay. Well, that song,
そのソング、そのソング、
that song...
友達は友達なんだ。
Friends are friends, right?
そう。
So,
It's a song from my favorite idol group,
Berryz工房。
Berryz Koubou.
私、Berryzオタクなので、そう。
I'm a Berry-otaku, so...
で、一緒に歌ってくれて、ありがとう。
And for you to sing it with me, thank you!
Berryzオタク、Berryzオタクとして、めっちゃ嬉しかった！
As a Berryz-otaku,
You are because you are otaku...
そういうことなの？
Is that what it is?
ねえ、あ、あと、
Well, also,
歌手も、
the singer...
めちゃくちゃ合うなと思ったし、
I thought she'd match really well,
あと曲のなんか元気さも、
and also the song's energy level
すばる先輩には合うかなと思ったから、
would match Subaru-senpai well,
この曲を選んだんです。
that's why I chose this song.
パワフルソング！
Powerful song!
Yeah, 元気ソング！
Yeah, Genki song!
Thank you!
Thank you too!
じゃあ、友達、だから友達っぽく帰りますか？
So, friends...
今まで友達じゃないみたいな、We are friends!
It's like we weren't even friends until now. We are...
ソロバード、ソロバード、ソロバード！
Sorobado, sorobado, sorobado!
Thank you!
え、じゃあ、
And then,
別のどこかに行くから、色々、Let's go!
we'll go somewhere else, so...
Let's go!
流れ星 願いを込めれば
Shooting star, if I place all my wishes into you
君に伝わるの
Would it reach you?
流れ星 願いを込めれば
Shooting star, if I place all my wishes into you
君に伝わるの
Would it reach you?
この街は 孤独なほど
This town is dissolving into the landscape
景色に溶け込んでく
So much that it's lonely
流れ星 頬に流れてる
Tears are flowing down my cheeks
私の涙よ
They are my own tears
悔しくて 泣んじやない
I'm not crying out of frustration
生きてる証なんだよ
This is just the proof that I am alive
胸を癒すような このメロディ
A melody that seems to heal my heart
ひとり だけども なぜか
Though I'm alone, somehow
ひとりじゃないような 気分になれる
I've come to not feel like I'm alone
流れ星 願いを込めれば
If I placed all my wishes into a shooting star,
君に伝わるの
would it reach you?
この街は 孤独な程
This town is dissolving into the landscape
景色に溶け込んでく
so much that it's lonely.
流れ星 頬に流れてる
Tears are flowing down my cheeks,
私の涙よ
they are my own tears.
悔しくて 泣んじじゃない
I'm not crying out of frustration,
生きている証なんだよ
this is just proof that I'm alive.
胸を癒すようなこのメロディ
A melody that seems to heal my heart,
気分になれる 今夜だけ一人じゃない
though I'm alone, somehow I don't feel alone.
悲しきヘブン 心が乾くけど
Sorrowful heaven, even though my heart is thirsty,
たった一つ 夢があるだけで私はそれで十分
as long as I just have one dream, I am satisfied.
セブンセブン いつかはたどり着く
Seventh heaven, someday I'll reach it,
この果てなき空を 行けば迷うこともある
if I go through this endless sky, I might get lost sometimes.
流れ星 都庁じゃ見えない現実の中で
Shooting star, amidst the reality unseen in the metropolis,
今夜だけ 一人じゃない そんな感じがしてる
tonight I feel like I'm not alone.
ため息で 言葉にならない瞬間もあるが
There are moments when a sigh leaves me speechless,
寂しくて 震えていた あの頃が懐かしいな
yet I fondly remember those days when I shivered in loneliness.
遠い過去なんてどうでもいい
The distant past doesn't matter,
明日に鳴れば きっと眩しい光 この手に 入る
tomorrow will surely bring a dazzling light into these hands.
悲しきヘブン 傷んだ翼でも
Sorrowful heaven, even with wounded wings,
それが叶うと信じなきゃ 私の意味がない
if I don't believe it will come true, there is no meaning to me.
セブンセブン 青いこの地球から 遠きゴール目指すだけさ
Seventh heaven, aiming for a distant goal from this blue Earth,
好きなことなら続く
things you love will go on.
悲しきヘブン 心が乾くけど
Sorrowful heaven, even though my heart is thirsty,
たった一つ 夢があるだけで
as long as I just have one dream,
私はそれで十分
I am satisfied with that.
セブンセブン いつかはたどり着く
Seventh heaven, someday I'll reach it,
この果てなき空を 行けば迷う こともある
if I go through this endless sky, I might get lost sometimes.
流れ星 願いを込めれば 君に伝わるの
Shooting star, if I put my wish into it, it will reach you.
この街は 孤独だけど 君と出会えた街だから
This town is lonely, but it's the town where I met you.
イェーイ！
Yay!
奇跡のキキ！運んでね！
Miracle Kiki! Bring it over!
運んでね！
Bring it over!
誰目当てのゲスト？マイセカンドゲストネチ！
Whose guest are you? My second guest, Netchi!
イェーイ！ももすずねねです！
Yay! I'm Momosuzu Nene!
踊れましたー！
We danced it!
できたねー！
We did it!
え、いいよ、かっこいいよ
Eh, it's good, it's cool!
かっこいいでしょ？
Cool, right?
かっこいいでしょ？かっこいいでしょ？どうも。
Cool, right? Cool, right? Hello.
かっこいいでしょ？
Cool, right?
はい、じゃあちょっと自己紹介できる？
Alright, so can you briefly introduce yourself?
ああ、えー、ホロライブ、フィフスジェネレーション...
Ah, um, Hololive Fifth Generation...
そう、ねね、ももすず…
That's right, Nene, Momosuzu...
ももすずー！イェーイ！
Momosuzu! Yay!
はい、まあうちの自己紹介もいらないよね？
Yes, well, we don't really need my self-introduction, right?
So actually, um, you guys probably know, together, people call us Orenzu.
Orenzuって呼ばれてるね、うちら。呼ばれてる、呼んでる？
We're called Orenzu. We're called that? You call us that?
まやも、呼ばれてるって言ったの！うちらが先にね、キモったよね。
Maya, you said we're called that! We came up with it first, right?
そう、名乗り出したからさ。うちらが先にね、キモったよね。
Yeah, we started calling ourselves that first.
その名乗り出したがや。
That's how it started.
So thank you for calling us Orenzu.
I I knew that if I had to call a guest, for my show, if I had to call a guest, who guest you you yobu dattara uchi no naka de zettai ni nenechi yobu shika nai to omotteta kara niwa futari de kanyu
I knew that if I had to call a guest for my show, if I had to call a guest, it had to be Nenechi! I knew I had to call her.
絶対にねねち呼ぶしかないとと思ってたからにわはるかんにゅう ね！うれしー！
I was so happy when you invited me, thinking I just had to call Nenechi!
イェーイ！うれしー！
Yay, I'm so happy!
So this is basically the first time that Orenzu is dancing together in 3D 初めてだよね？はじめてって可愛い！うっきょうるじょ！
So this is basically the first time that Orenzu is dancing together in 3D, right?
初めてだ、可愛い！よく踊れたねー！
First time, so cute! We danced so well!
可愛い！可愛い！可愛い！ねっちの方が可愛い！
Cute! Cute! Cute! Nene is cuter!
いやだ、いやだ、いやだ！
No way, no way, no way!
ということで、はい、初めてのおれんずということで、あの、やっぱりお互い、どっちもアイドル好きでしょ？
So, as our first time as Orenzu, you know, we both love idols, right?
I love idol, you love idol, We are idols. So, I want to create some kind of like idol boy greeting aisatsu
I love idol, you love idol, we are idols. So, I want to create some kind of like idol-boy greeting, aisatsu.
考えたいな。
I want to think of one.
そう、考え、考えちゃう
Right, you keep thinking about it.
そうね、それをずっとやる
That's right, you keep doing it.
やり続ける
Keep doing it continuously.
オッケーオッケー。ここ、じゃあ大事だねこれ。
Okay, okay. So this part is important, right?
オッケー。
Okay.
で、そういうことで、うんうんうんどうする？
So, with that being said... um um um, what should we do?
なんか、テーマみたいな、オレンジのテーマ。
Like, a theme, an orange theme.
オレンジでしょ？オレンジで。
Orange, right? Orange.
オレンジ！オレンジ！
Orange! Orange!
なんかこう、グローバルな感じがいいな。
Something like... a global vibe would be nice.
はいはい。グローバル、インターナショナル？オッケー。
Right, right. Global, international? Okay.
ソー、ハウアバウト、ウィーメイクザホールワールドオレンジ？
So, how about we make the whole world orange?
おお、いいね。世界をオレンジ色に、そう、染め上げるとか、染めていくとか、どう？
Oh, nice. Dyeing the whole world orange... right, like dyeing it or coloring it, how's that?
おおじゃあ染め、染めちゃうにしよう。染めちゃうで！オッケーオッケー。
Oh, then let's make it "dye it". Let's go with "dye it"! Okay, okay.
おじゃあ動きも、動き、どんな動きにする？
Oh, then the movement too, movement, what kind of movement?
ムニツムーブメント、うーん。え？
Nenechi movement, um... Eh?
え、世界観出したほうがいい？
Eh, should we bring out the worldview?
世界！世界！世界を！
The world! The world! The world!
オレンジ色に、染め、染めちゃう！オレンジでス！
Orange, dye, let's dye it! It's orange!
オレンジで！オレンジで！オレンジです！
Orange! Orange! It's orange!
これでいく？動き戻った。もう一回やってみよう。
Are we going with this? Movement is back. Let's try it again.
ちゃんと、正式に。はい。
Properly, officially. Yes.
世界も！オレンジ色に！染め、染めちゃう！オレンジでス！
The world too! Orange! Dye, let's dye it! It's orange!
もう、また染めたいって言ったよ。まあいいよ、ええよ、ええよ。
There you go, you said you wanted to dye it again. Well, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
これ、ずっとやるのか、今後。そうやるの、まあ忘れちゃいけない。
Are we gonna keep doing this from now on? Yeah, we are. Well, don't forget.
Don't forget, this is our official greeting now. Yay! Yay!
え、じゃあ、ワンモアシング？
Eh, then, one more thing?
え、Let's talk about the song and our practice and all that.
Um, let's talk about the song and our practice and all that.
この曲についてと練習について、語ろう。
Let's talk about this song and our practice.
お、まずね、Kanashiki HEAVEN is a Neverland Project song. I love Hello Project, and this is from Cute, the idol group Cuteね。あいCuteね、好きだもんね。
Oh, first, "Kanashiki HEAVEN" is a Hello Project song. I love Hello Project, and this is from C-ute, the idol group C-ute, right? I love C-ute, right?
Yeah, and it's very dramatic, sad song with a strong dance move, strong choreographyね、あの、激しい振り付けだったね。
Yeah, and it's a very dramatic, sad song with strong dance moves and choreography, right? The choreography was intense.
ああ、そうなの。やばかったよ、もう。
Ah, that's right. It was crazy, seriously.
ただ、うちは、うん、2時間でできた。覚えました。
But, as for us, um, we finished it in two hours. We memorized it.
Two hours, we had two hours of dance lessons together.
Yeah, eh, the dance, dance teacher was like, "Oh, you guys are learning it so quickly!" and she was happy. ダンスの先生がね、早く覚えてて、ね、褒めてくれたんです、すごい。すごい早い！って言われたよね。ねえ。
Yeah, eh, the dance teacher was like, "Oh, you guys are learning it so quickly!" and praised us so much. She told us, "You're so fast!" Right?
でもうちも、Nenechiと、のダンスレッスンは、楽だろうと思って、楽しみにしてた。でも、すっごい楽しみしてた。でもさ、朝だったからさ。
But we thought Nenechi's dance lessons would be easy, so we were looking forward to it. We were really looking forward to it. But you know, it was morning.
朝じゃないよ、昼だって。昼じゃないよ、夕方だよ、昼過ぎてた。え、ねえねえにとっては、昼は朝。なるほど。
It wasn't morning, it was noon. It wasn't noon, it was evening, it was past noon. Eh, for Nenechi, noon is morning. I see.
はい。え、苦労した振り付けとかある？
Yes. Eh, were there any choreography parts you struggled with?
この2番の、これ、ねえ、この動きね。パンパン。
This second part, this, right, this movement. Bam bam.
あれ難しいよね、で、だって、早いから。で、ここも難しかった、ジャンジャンジャン、ジャン。早いから、バーン。できているか。あ、違う、早いからな。ゆっくりやるとすごい綺麗にできるんだけど、
That's difficult, right? Because, you know, it's fast. And this part was also difficult, chan chan chan, chan. Because it's fast, bam. Are we doing it? Ah, no, because it's fast. If you do it slowly, you can do it really cleanly,
大変だったけど、でも比べればスパン！And I hope we can do more.難しかったけど。
it was tough, but compared to that, span! And I hope we can do more. Even though it was difficult.
もっとやりたい！オレンジで！もっとやりたい、お願いします、お願いします。ねえねえこっそりさん、お願いします。ねえねえお願いします。せーの。
I want to do more! In orange! I want to do more, please, please. Hey hey Secret-san, please. Hey hey please. Ready.
はい、オレンジもよろしく。はい、よろしく。というわけで、I'm I'm gonna send off Nenechi, so we're gonna change location. Nenechi will とりあえず送り出す。
Yes, orange too, please. Yes, please. So, I'm gonna send off Nenechi, so we're gonna change location. Nenechi will see you off for now.
オッケー！いってらっしゃい！いってらっしゃい！
Okay! Have a good time! Have a good time!
はあー。オッケー。
Haa. Okay.
バーン！Welcome back to KFP, guys!
Bam! Welcome back to KFP, guys!
I'm sorry, it's not over yet. I have something really important for you guys,
and that is... What could it be? What could it be? That's right, merchandise!
Okay, let me introduce to you. I mean, you know, there's burgers and all that, but this time, very special,
time limited offer for you guys.
タァーッ！ It is the beautiful Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle & Bottle Case Set!
Ta-da! It is the beautiful Hot Phoenix Thermo Bottle & Bottle Case Set!
That's right, it comes with like, kind of like a bag for the thermos bottle. I already saw it in reality, and it looks so good!
Yay! And of course, it's fermus, which means your hot drinks will stay hot, and your cold drinks will stay cold!
Yay! And of course, it's thermos, which means your hot drinks will stay hot, and your cold drinks will stay cold!
Perfect genius! Oh my god!
Special 3D merchandise for this occasion,
and... and there's something else that I want to tell you about, tomorrow... tomorrow!
Yes, tomorrow at 6:00 p.m. JST,
my very first hologravure is coming out!
As Takalocuisine, heed us! Yoroshiku onegaishimasu, yoru, yoru no 6-ji.
Then, well... and of course, tomorrow is also the 3D debut of Takanashi Kiari! So go check her out, okay? It's Takanashi weekend! Yay!
So, besides that, I have one more song for you guys,
but I think we should change location, is that okay?
Change, change, alright!
This is one more stage that I haven't shown you guys yet, which is the big whole live English stage!
Let's go!
Ah... ah... that video... I did not give the permission to show that video! Why did you show that video?!
I wasn't slacking, I was practicing!
Well, I am here on this beautiful EN stage right now
to perform one last song! But before that, I want to say thank you guys so much for waiting for such a long time, two and a half years, I think, roughly...
to... till we got to this point, which is unusually long, but yeah.
We all were patient and I think it was worth it. I hope so, wasn't it worth it?
Well, I practiced really hard for this day and I tried really hard to fix my throat for this day.
So, I hope you guys enjoyed it. It was a very special day for me. I was really nervous, but I hope I could show you...
all the beautiful parts, all the good things about Takanashi Kiara!
Yeah, let's do more in the future, okay?
Okay, so with that, the last song... Do U!
Ooh...
I don't wanna stop it yet
Playin' Russian Roulette
Yeah boy as soon as I saw you I knew it
Baby it's you, oh ya, now
Got me love drunk I'm knocked down, down, down
There's somethin' special about you
When I see you I know it's true
Oh ya, now
Gotta getta ya, oh ya, now, now, now
If it ain't you baby then I'm done
Yeah yeah oh girl, you know it!
I just can't resist you
Your eyes are like a spell that I can't break through
And that should scare me
But I don't know baby
You're captivating me and in the end you'll let me go
That's just what we do...
Love, hate all the same
If you know play the game I'm all locked up-up inside
No I can't fight the feeling and I won't try
All the same, if you know play the game
Baby you decide
If you want me then shout it out right now!!
Love is just a game I can't complain
I do the same, oh!
Do u? Do u?
Say you do feel the same
Spark me like a flame
I know I'll never be the same, oh!
Do u? Do u?
In the end love's just all a game
Don't ever let yourself fall in
You got it?
'Cause love's just like a toxin
The way pain is so common
Your problem, I can't...
can't solve it!
I'm just a fool in love,
know that this is more than a crush,
so you can't save me,
I'm in too deep,
and I love the rush, yeah.
I just can't resist you.
Your eyes are like a spell that I can't break through,
and that should scare me.
But I don't know, baby, you're captivating me,
and in the end you'll let me go.
Love, hate, all the same.
If you know, play the game.
I'm all locked up inside.
No, I can't fight the feeling and I won't try.
Love, hate, all the same.
If you know, play the game.
Baby, you decide if you want me, then shout it out right now!
Love is just a game.
I can't complain, I do the same, oh!
Do you? Do you say you do feel the same?
Spark me like a flame, I know I'll never be the same, oh!
Do you? Do you? In the end, love's just all a game.
Got me breathless, oh, yeah.
I'm by your night and day, how can somethin' so wrong
be makin' me feel so right? Breakin' me down, down.
Pick me up just like you do, I'm always coming back to you.
Love is just a game, I can't complain, I do the same, oh!
Do you? Do you say you do feel the same?
Spark me like a flame, I know I'll never be the same, oh!
Do you? Do you? In the end, love's just all a game.
Love is just a game we play. Love, hate, trust, then betray.
Do you? Do you say you do feel the same?
Do you? Do you? In the end, love's just all a game.